{"status":"Success","data":{"general_datas":[{"q_number":"21","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02?\r\n","answer":"\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f "},{"q_number":"22","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d21 "},{"q_number":"23","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7b \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02?\r\n","answer":"\u0d38\u0d41\u0d21\u0d3e\u0d7b "},{"q_number":"24","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02?\r\n","answer":"\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28 "},{"q_number":"25","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02?\r\n","answer":"\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b "},{"q_number":"66","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d2c\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28"},{"q_number":"67","question":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7a"},{"q_number":"72","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ______ ?","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d7e"},{"q_number":"73","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2c\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"74","question":"\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d14\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d38\u0d24\u0d3f ?","answer":"10 \u0d21\u0d57\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"75","question":"\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d14\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d38\u0d24\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02"},{"q_number":"127","question":"\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d40\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d42\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d46"},{"q_number":"128","question":"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d47"},{"q_number":"633","question":"\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d46\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d46\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d17\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"634","question":"\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d46\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d?\r\n","answer":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\r\n"},{"q_number":"635","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d05\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d (\u0d17\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d)\r\n"},{"q_number":"636","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d05\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d27\u0d38\u0d48\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d30\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28(2-\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d)\r\n"},{"q_number":"703","question":"\u201d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d40\u0d30\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d20\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d35\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u201d \u2013 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e ?","answer":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"704","question":"\u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d36\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d30\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"705","question":"\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d15\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d32\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"706","question":"\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d38\u0d40\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d07\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"707","question":"\u0d1c\u0d42\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d14\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d0f\u0d15 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d32\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"708","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d39\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ? ","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b"},{"q_number":"709","question":"\u201d\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d28\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d30\u0d42, \u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d02\u201d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e ?","answer":"\u0d28\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"710","question":"\u0d2c\u0d4a\u0d33\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d21\u0d2f\u0d31\u0d3f \u2013 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d46\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d17\u0d41\u0d35\u0d47\u0d30"},{"q_number":"711","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f"},{"q_number":"712","question":"\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ,\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d02, \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d02"},{"q_number":"713","question":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2b\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d7d"},{"q_number":"714","question":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d16\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02.?","answer":"AD 1221"},{"q_number":"715","question":"\u0d36\u0d24\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30 \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ? ","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"716","question":"\u0d05\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7e \u0d39\u0d4b \u2013 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d05\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d7b ?","answer":"\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"717","question":"\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d40\u0d28 \u0d36\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d17\u0d02"},{"q_number":"718","question":"\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d23\u0d41\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"1945"},{"q_number":"719","question":"\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e \u0d05\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27 \u0d38\u0d48\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d.? ","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"720","question":"\u0d24\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47 \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d34\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d24 .?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02"},{"q_number":"721","question":"\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2b\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ? ","answer":"\u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"722","question":"\u0d35\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28"},{"q_number":"723","question":"\u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d24\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"724","question":"\u0d1c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d7e \u0d39\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7c \u0d24\u0d41\u0d31\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ? ","answer":"1941"},{"q_number":"725","question":"\u0d1a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d40\u0d24 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d15\u0d24\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ","answer":" \u0d28\u0d35\u0d40\u0d28 \u0d36\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d17\u0d02"},{"q_number":"726","question":"\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02"},{"q_number":"727","question":"\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d46\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"728","question":"\u0d38\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u201d \u0d0e\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f \u201d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d31\u0d42\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4b"},{"q_number":"729","question":"\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d27\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15"},{"q_number":"730","question":"\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2b\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d39\u0d4b\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d31\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02"},{"q_number":"731","question":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ? ","answer":"AD 1398\r\n"},{"q_number":"732","question":"1492 \u0d07\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d2b\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d33\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"733","question":"\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d48\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d21\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d21\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d46"},{"q_number":"734","question":"\u0d06\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2f\u0d42\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d17\u0d40\u0d38\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"735","question":"\u0d1c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24 \u0d30\u0d40\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d07\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d28"},{"q_number":"736","question":"\u0d38\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d35\u0d41\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"737","question":"\u0d12\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d35\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ? ","answer":"\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d02"},{"q_number":"738","question":" \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 ? ","answer":"\u0d28\u0d35\u0d40\u0d28 \u0d36\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d17\u0d02"},{"q_number":"739","question":"\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d35\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d47\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d48\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d32\u0d46\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"740","question":"\u201c\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d \u201d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d40\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d40\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"741","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d1c\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"742","question":"\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2b\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"1848"},{"q_number":"743","question":"\u0d2e\u0d57 \u0d2e\u0d57 \u0d32\u0d39\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ? ","answer":"\u0d15\u0d46\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f"},{"q_number":"744","question":"\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d05\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"745","question":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d46 \u0d31\u0d46\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d33\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"746","question":"\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d21\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d16\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"747","question":"\u201d \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d42 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u201d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d14\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"748","question":"\u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d35\u0d02 ? ","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d02"},{"q_number":"749","question":"\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ? ","answer":"1991"},{"q_number":"750","question":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d35\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d16\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d48\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d3f ? ","answer":"\u0d13\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d46\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d21\u0d38\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d02"},{"q_number":"751","question":"\u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d48\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4c\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"752","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d36\u0d40\u0d32 \u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d46\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ? ","answer":"1954"},{"q_number":"753","question":"\u0d06\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27 \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d24\u0d43 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d18\u0d3e\u0d28\r\n"},{"q_number":"754","question":"\u201c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u201d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d08 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d35\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d .?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d02"},{"q_number":"755","question":"\u201d \u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d3f \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d , \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23\u0d02 , \u0d05\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d4a\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d , \u0d0e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u201d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d02\r\n"},{"q_number":"756","question":"\u0d05\u0d31\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ? ","answer":"AD 712"},{"q_number":"757","question":"\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d21\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d36\u0d41\u0d2d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"1488"},{"q_number":"758","question":"\u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d48\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37 ?","answer":"\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"759","question":"\u201d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d41\u0d34\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46 \u201d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4b \u0d38\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d42\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"760","question":"\u0d07\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"1948"},{"q_number":"761","question":"\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d41\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"762","question":"1863 \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d05\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"763","question":"\u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d36\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d40\u0d28 \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d7b\u0d15"},{"q_number":"764","question":"\u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d2d\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30 \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"AD 1642"},{"q_number":"765","question":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ? ","answer":"AD 1776"},{"q_number":"766","question":"\u0d08\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d2c\u0d4d \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"1958"},{"q_number":"767","question":"\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ? ","answer":"1966"},{"q_number":"768","question":"\u0d2b\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"769","question":"\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"1688"},{"q_number":"770","question":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f \u201d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"771","question":"\u0d1c\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d30\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"772","question":"\u0d07\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d40\u0d28\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"773","question":"\u0d26\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d36 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d08\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"774","question":"\u0d06\u0d27\u0d41\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d15\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b \u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d16\u0d41\u0d2b\u0d41"},{"q_number":"775","question":"\u0d06\u0d27\u0d41\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d1a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"776","question":"\u0d08\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d31\u0d35\u0d4b"},{"q_number":"777","question":"\u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d39\u0d41\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"778","question":"\u0d38\u0d57\u0d30 \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d17\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d08\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"779","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37 ? ","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"780","question":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d02"},{"q_number":"781","question":"\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d38\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"782","question":"\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d23\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"783","question":"\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7a \u0d1f\u0d40 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ? ","answer":"AD 1773"},{"q_number":"784","question":"\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d17\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d38\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"785","question":"\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d28\u0d35\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d42\u0d24\u0d30\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"786","question":"\u201d\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d31\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d3f \u201d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02"},{"q_number":"787","question":"\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d7c\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d \u2013 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"788","question":"\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"1789"},{"q_number":"789","question":"\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d32\u0d35\u0d4b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d46"},{"q_number":"790","question":"\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ","answer":"\u0d35\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"791","question":"\u201c\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d . \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d32\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u201d \u2013 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d31\u0d42\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4b"},{"q_number":"792","question":"\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d36\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d41 ? ","answer":"\u0d28\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"793","question":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d42\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d40\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d35\u0d48\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"794","question":"\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d30\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d46\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d17\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7b ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d17\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d28\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"795","question":"\u0d38\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d15\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d32 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"796","question":"\u0d28\u0d35\u0d4b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46"},{"q_number":"797","question":"\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d36\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d02"},{"q_number":"798","question":"\u2018\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d\u2019 \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"799","question":"\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d15\u0d7b ?","answer":"\u0d31\u0d42\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4b"},{"q_number":"800","question":"\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4b\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d38 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d4b \u0d21\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"801","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d40\u0d02\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d28\u0d47\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f"},{"q_number":"802","question":"\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f"}]},"code":"100"}